

Resume FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Personal details

Abdulwasiu Oladimeji Saliman



Salimanoladimeji33gmail.com



+2348068525022



Area 11 police cantoment Garki 900247 Abuja



January 31st, 1999



Male



Nigerian



github.com/oladimeji-dev



linkedin.com/in/abdulwasiusaliman-507193239

OBJECTIVE

A front-end developer with extensive experience in building responsive websites and web applications. I am experienced in working with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React.js.I have a passion for creating user-friendly interfaces and strive to build websites that are both visually appealing and easy to use. I have a strong understanding of front-end development technologies and principles of user experience design.

To contribute my experience and problem-solving skills to achieve the organizational goals and objectives by going the extra mile and exceeding my employer's expectations.

Education

2012 - 2015 Secondary school

GDSS WUSE II, ABUJA

2015 - 2017 National Diploma (ND)

Kwara State Polytechnic, Ilorin

Computer Science

2018 - 2021 Higher National Diploma

Kwara State Polytechnic, abuja

Computer Science

HARD SKILL

HTML & CSS

Javascript

React.Js

Bootstrap

GIT

Node.js Beginner

SOFT SKILL

Problem-Solving Very good

Analytical and Critical

Thinking

Very good

Team work and

Collaboration

Excellent

Time management Very good

Employment

2016 - 2017 Computer Hardware Engineer

AITLINKS Tech, Ilorin

I was in charge of repairing and troubleshooting

desktop computer .

INTEREST

- Learning
- Coding
- Innovation
- Reading
- Music

2017 - 2018

Data Entry

National Bureau Of Statistics(NBS), Abuja

Web Developer

Freelance, Abuja

Contributed to building responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery.
Collaborated with web designers and back-end developers to create user-friendly web applications.
Optimized web pages for maximum speed and compatibility across different browsers and devices.

2022 - 2022

Web Developer

and also the location.

Freelance, Abuja this was a coffee website for the owner for display